Guide to the Cornell University Cooperative Extension records, 1915-2009.
Cornell University Cooperative Extension records, 1915-2009.
- Series III. Publications
  - Papers, Articles and Flyers
    - Cooperative Extension in New York City-articles, flyers, publications, 1993-1994 (Box 58, Folder 21)
    - Cooperative Extension in New York City-articles, flyers, publications, 1994 (Box 58, Folder 22)
    - Cooperative Extension in New York City - publications, 2007 (Box 58, Folder 22A)
    - Cooperative Extension in New York City - publications, 2000-2009 (Box 89, Folder 16)
    - Papers - History of Cooperative Extension, 2000-2009 (Box 89, Folder 17)
    - Medicare Part D pocket guide to prescriptiion drug plan comparisons, 2007-10 (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - Cooperative Extension Notes
    - Cornell Cooperative Extension Notes, #20-67, 1984-1989 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Cornell Cooperative Extension Notes, #68-91, 1990-1991 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Cornell Cooperative Extension Notes, #92-121, 1992-1994 (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Cornell Cooperative Extension Notes, #122-129, 1995 (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Cornell Cooperative Extension Notes, #130-139, 1996 (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - Cornell Cooperative Extension Notes, #140-145, 1997 (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - Cornell Cooperative Extension Notes, #146-149, 1997-1998 (Box 50, Folder 14)
    - Cornell Cooperative Extension Notes, #150-154, 1998 (Box 50, Folder 15)
    - Cornell Cooperative Extension Notes, 1999 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Discussion Papers
    - Strengthening the CCE System Discussion Paper, 1989 (Box 49, Folder 36)
    - Director Bill Lacy, Biography, 1994-1998 (Box 50, Folder 17)
      includes photos and news articles
    - Discussion Paper: Placing a Value on Extension, 1993-06 (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - Discussion Paper: Putting the Diversity Advantage to Work, 1994 (Box 50, Folder 18)
    - Discussion Paper: Positive Leadership for Dealing with Limited Resources, 1994 (Box 50, Folder 19)
    - Discussion Paper: Continuity and Change in the University Without Walls, 1994 (Box 50, Folder 20)
    - Discussion Paper: Public Policy Education Statement of Principles for the Cornell Cooperative Extension System, 1994 (Box 50, Folder 21)
    - Discussion Paper: Working with Local Governments in New York State, 1994 (Box 50, Folder 22)
    - Discussion Paper: Building Successful Coalitions, 1994 (Box 50, Folder 23)
    - Discussion Paper: Leadership, 1994 (Box 50, Folder 24)
    - Discussion Paper: Working Toward the Diversity Advantage, 1994 (Box 50, Folder 25)
    - Discussion Paper: Strengthening 4-H Youth Development Work in the Cornell Cooperative Extension System, 1994 (Box 50, Folder 26)
    - Discussion Paper: Cornell Cooperative Extension Program Excellence- Support Through Inservice Education, 1994 (Box 50, Folder 27)
    - Discussion Paper: Reorganization- Where do we Start?, 1994 (Box 50, Folder 28)
    - Discussion Paper: Issue Work, 1994 (Box 50, Folder 29)
    - Discussion Paper: Putting the Diversity Advantage to Work, 1994 (Box 50, Folder 30)
    - Discussion Papers, 1989-1997 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - Statewide Economic Vitality Program, 1990-1994 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Increasing Economic Development Statewide: Program Initiative Work Group Reports and Recommendations, 1990 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - Increasing Economic Development Committee Report, 1989 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - On the Extension Line (OTEL) Perspectives
    - (OTEL)and Perspectives, 1968-06-1968-07, 1968-09-1968-12 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - OTEL and Perspectives, 1969-01-1969-06 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - OTEL and Perspectives, 1969-07-1969-12 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - OTEL and Perspectives, 1970-01-1970-04 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - OTEL and Perspectives, 1970-05-1970-08 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - OTEL and Perspectives, 1970-09-1970-12 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - OTEL and Perspectives, 1971-01-1971-03 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - OTEL and Perspectives, 1971-04-1971-06 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - OTEL and Perspectives, 1971-07-1971-09 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - OTEL and Perspectives, 1971-10-1971-12 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - OTEL and Perspectives, 1972-01-1972-05 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - OTEL and Perspectives, 1972-06, 1972-09-1972-12 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - OTEL and Perspectives, 1973-01-1973-06 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - OTEL and Perspectives, 1973-07-1973-12 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - OTEL and Perspectives, 1974-01-1974-03 (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - OTEL and Perspectives, 1974-04-1974-06 (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - OTEL and Perspectives, 1974-07-1974-11 (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - OTEL and Perspectives, 1975-06, 1975-09 (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - OTEL and Perspectives, 1977-01, 1977-03, 1977-06, 1977-09, 1977-11 (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - OTEL and Perspectives, 1978-01, 1978-03, 1978-05, 1978-07, 1978-09, 1978-11 (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - OTEL and Perspectives, 1979-01-1979-05 (Box 39, Folder 21)
    - OTEL and Perspectives, 1979-07-1979-11 (Box 39, Folder 22)
    - OTEL and Perspectives, 1980-03, 1980-05, 1980-07, 1980-09, 1980-11 (Box 39, Folder 23)
    - OTEL and Perspectives: v.XIII no.1-5, 1981 (Box 39, Folder 24)
    - OTEL and Perspectives: v.XIV no.1-3,5, 1982 (Box 39, Folder 25)
    - OTEL and Perspectives: v.XV no.1-5, 1983 (Box 39, Folder 26)
    - OTEL and Perspectives: v.XVI no.1-5, 1984 (Box 39, Folder 27)
    - OTEL and Perspectives: v.XVII no.1-5, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 28)
    - OTEL and Perspectives v.XVIII no.1-3, 1986-01, 1986-03, 1986-06 (Box 39, Folder 29)
    - OTEL and Perspectives v.XVIII no.4-8, 1986-08-1986-12 (Box 39, Folder 30)
    - OTEL and Perspectives v.IXX no.1-4, 1987-01-1987-04 (Box 39, Folder 31)
    - OTEL and Perspectives v.IXX no.5,6,6-9, 1987-05-1987-12 (Box 39, Folder 32)
    - OTEL and Perspectives v.XX no.1-10, 1988-01-1988-12 (Box 39, Folder 33)
    - OTEL and Perspectives v.XXI no.1-4, 1989-01-1989-04 (Box 39, Folder 34)
    - OTEL and Perspectives v.XXI no.5-10, 1989-05-1989-12 (Box 39, Folder 35)
    - OTEL and Perspectives v.XXII no.1-5, 1990-01-1990-05 (Box 39, Folder 36)
    - OTEL and Perspectives v.XXII no.6-10, 1990-06-1990-12 (Box 39, Folder 37)
    - OTEL and Perspectives v.XXII no.11, 1991-01 (Box 39, Folder 38)
    - OTEL and Perspectives v.XXIII no.1-4, 1991-02-1991-05 (Box 39, Folder 38)
    - OTEL and Perspectives v.XXIII no.5-8, 1991-07-1991-12 (Box 39, Folder 39)
    - OTEL and Perspectives v.XXIV no.1-9, 1992-01-1992-06, 1992-08, 1992-10-1992-12 (Box 39, Folder 40)
    - OTEL and Perspectives v.I no.1, 1987-10 (Box 39, Folder 41)
    - OTEL and Perspectives v.II no.1-4, 1988-03-1988-04, 1988-08, 1988-10 (Box 39, Folder 42)
    - OTEL and Perspectives v.III no.1,2, 1989-02, 1989-08 (Box 39, Folder 43)
    - OTEL and Perspectives v.IV no.2,3, 1990-05, 1990-10 (Box 39, Folder 44)
    - OTEL and Perspectives v.V no.1,3, 1991-01-1991-10 (Box 39, Folder 45)
    - OTEL and Perspectives v.VI no.6, 1992-05 (Box 39, Folder 46)
- Series IV. Initiatives, Plans, Projects, Reports
  - County Annual Reports
  - Albany County Annual Reports, 1944-1960 (Box 13, Folder 1-17)
  - Albany County Annual Reports, 1997,1998,2000 (Box 67)
  - Allegany County Annual Reports, 1944-1960 (Box 13, Folder 18-34)
  - Allegany County Annual Reports, 1996-2000 (Box 67)
  - Broome County Annual Reports, 1944-1946 (Box 13, Folder 35-37)
  - Broome County Annual Reports, 1995-2000 (Box 67)
  - Broome County Annual Reports, 1947-1960 (Box 14, Folder 1-14)
  - Broome County Program of Work, 1956 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Buffalo Annual Reports, 1944-1951, 1953 (Box 37, Folder 14-22)
  - Cattaraugus County Annual Reports, 1944-1960 (Box 14, Folder 16-32)
  - Cattaraugus County Annual Reports, 1996-2000 (Box 67)
  - Cayuga County Annual Reports, 1944-1951 (Box 14, Folder 33-40)
  - Cayuga County Annual Reports, 1952-1960 (Box 15, Folder 1-9)
  - Cayuga County Annual Reports, 1995-1997,2000 (Box 67)
  - Chautauqua County Annual Reports, 1944-1960 (Box 15, Folder 10-26)
  - Chautauqua County Annual Reports, 1993,1996,1997,1999,2000 (Box 67)
  - Chemung County Annual Reports, 1944-1953 (Box 15, Folder 27-36)
  - Chemung County Annual Reports, 1954-1960 (Box 16, Folder 1-7)
  - Chemung County Annual Reports, 1996-2000 (Box 67)
  - Chenango County Annual Reports, 1944-1960 (Box 16, Folder 8-24)
  - Chenango County Annual Reports, 1997 (Box 67)
  - Clinton County Annual Reports, 1944-1960 (Box 16, Folder 25-41)
  - Clinton County Annual Reports, 1993, 1995-1999 (Box 67)
  - Columbia County Annual Reports, 1946-1960 (Box 17, Folder 1-15)
  - Columbia County Annual Reports, 1996-2001 (Box 67)
  - Cortland County Annual Reports, 1944-1960 (Box 17, Folder 16-32)
  - Cortland County Annual Reports, 1990-1994, 1997,1999,2000 (Box 67)
  - Delaware County Annual Reports, 1944-1949 (Box 17, Folder 33-38)
  - Delaware County Annual Reports, 1950-1960 (Box 18, Folder 1-11)
  - Delaware County Annual Reports, 1993, 1995-2001 (Box 67)
  - Dutchess County Annual Reports, 1943, 1945-1960 (Box 18, Folder 12-28)
  - Dutchess County Annual Reports, 1991, 1993, 1995, 1996, 1998-2000 (Box 67)
  - Erie County Annual Reports, 1944-1949 (Box 18, Folder 29-34)
  - Erie County Annual Reports, 1950-1960 (Box 19, Folder 1-11)
  - Erie County Annual Reports, 1993,1996,1998 (Box 67)
  - Essex County Annual Reports, 1948-1960 (Box 19, Folder 12-24)
  - Essex County Annual Reports, 1993,1996-2000 (Box 67)
  - Franklin County Annual Reports, 1944-1960 (Box 19, Folder 25-41)
  - Franklin County Annual Reports, 1993, 1995-2001 (Box 67)
  - Fulton County Annual Reports, 1942, 1950-1960 (Box 20, Folder 1-12)
  - Fulton County Annual Reports, 1992, 1993, 1995, 1996, 1998-2000 (Box 67)
  - Genessee County Annual Reports, 1947-1960 (Box 20, Folder 13-26)
  - Genessee County Annual Reports, 1988, 1997-2000 (Box 67)
  - Greene County Annual Reports, 1993, 1995-2000 (Box 67)
  - Hamilton County Annual Report, 1942 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Hamilton County Annual Report, 1993, 1995-1998, 2000 (Box 67)
  - Herkimer County Annual Reports, 1944-1955 (Box 20, Folder 28-39)
  - Herkimer County Annual Reports, 1956-1960 (Box 21, Folder 1-5)
  - Herkimer County Annual Reports, 1995-2000 (Box 67)
  - Jefferson County Annual Reports, 1944-1960 (Box 21, Folder 6-22)
  - Jefferson County Annual Reports, 1987, 1991, 1993, 1995, 1996-1998 (Box 67)
  - Lewis County Annual Reports, 1944-1960 (Box 21, Folder 23-39)
  - Lewis County Annual Reports, 1986, 1999-2001 (Box 67)
  - Livingston County Annual Reports, 1944-1960 (Box 22, Folder 1-17)
  - Livingston County Annual Reports, 1991, 1997-2001 (Box 67)
  - Madison County Annual Reports, 1944-1960 (Box 22, Folder 18-34)
  - Madison County Annual Reports, 1996-2000 (Box 67)
  - Monroe County Annual Reports, 1944-1947 (Box 22, Folder 35-38)
  - Monroe County Annual Reports, 1948-1960 (Box 23, Folder 1-13)
  - Monroe County Annual Reports, 1997-2001 (Box 67)
  - Montgomery County Annual Reports, 1918, 1945-1960 (Box 23, Folder 14-30)
  - Montgomery County Annual Reports, 1992, 1993, 1995, 1996, 1998-2000 (Box 67)
  - Nassau County Annual Reports, 1944-1959 (Box 24, Folder 1-16)
  - Nassau County Annual Reports, 1997,1999 (Box 67)
  - Niagara County Annual Reports, 1944-1960 (Box 24, Folder 17-33)
  - Niagara County Annual Reports, 1997-2000 (Box 67)
  - Oneida County Annual Reports, 1944-1946 (Box 24, Folder 34-36)
  - Oneida County Annual Reports, 1947-1960 (Box 25, Folder 1-14)
  - Oneida County Annual Reports, 1992-1993, 1995-1998, 2000-2001 (Box 67)
  - Onondaga County Annual Reports, 1944-1960 (Box 25, Folder 15-31)
  - Onondaga County Annual Reports, 1992-1993, 1995-1997, 2000-2001 (Box 67)
  - Ontario County Annual Reports, 1944-1960 (Box 26, Folder 1-17)
  - Ontario County Annual Reports, 1993, 1996-2000 (Box 67)
  - Orange County Annual Reports, 1944-1960 (Box 26, Folder 18-34)
  - Orange County Annual Reports, 1993, 1997-2000 (Box 67)
  - Orleans County Annual Reports, 1944-1960 (Box 27, Folder 1-17)
  - Orleans County Annual Reports, 1989, 1992-1993, 1996-2001 (Box 67)
  - Oswego County Annual Reports, 1944-1960 (Box 27, Folder 18-34)
  - Oswego County Annual Reports, 1997-2001 (Box 27, Folder 18-34)
  - Otsego County Annual Reports, 1946-1949 (Box 27, Folder 35-38)
  - Otsego County Annual Reports, 1950-1960 (Box 28, Folder 1-11)
  - Otsego County Annual Reports, 1988, 1993, 1995-1999 (Box 67)
  - Putnam County Annual Report, 1942 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Putnam County Annual Report, 1989,1992-1993, 1995-2000 (Box 67)
  - Rensselaer County Annual Reports, 1944-1960 (Box 28, Folder 13-29)
  - Rensselaer County Annual Reports, 1993,1997-2001 (Box 67)
  - Rochester Annual Reports, 1940, 1944-1954 (Box 37, Folder 23-34)
  - Rochester Annual Reports, 1955-1960 (Box 38, Folder 1-6)
  - Rockland County Annual Reports, 1947-1955 (Box 28, Folder 30-38)
  - Rockland County Annual Reports, 1956-1960 (Box 29, Folder 1-5)
  - Rockland County Annual Reports, 1995-1997, 1999-2001 (Box 67)
  - St. Lawrence County Annual Reports, 1944-1960 (Box 29, Folder 6-22)
  - St. Lawrence County Annual Reports, 1998-2000 (Box 67)
  - Saratoga County Annual Reports, 1944-1953 (Box 29, Folder 23-32)
  - Saratoga County Annual Reports, 1954-1960 (Box 30, Folder 1-7)
  - Saratoga County Annual Reports, 1992,1995-1998,2000 (Box 67)
  - Schenectady County Annual Reports, 1944-1960 (Box 30, Folder 8-24)
  - Schenectady County Annual Reports, 1993, 1996-1998, 2000 (Box 67)
  - Schoharie County Annual Reports, 1944-1953 (Box 30, Folder 25-34)
  - Schoharie County Annual Reports, 1954-1960 (Box 31, Folder 1-7)
  - Schoharie County Annual Reports, 1993, 1995-2001 (Box 67)
  - Schuyler County Annual Reports, 1946-1960 (Box 31, Folder 8-22)
  - Schuyler County Annual Reports, 1996-2001 (Box 68)
  - Seneca County Annual Reports, 1946-1960 (Box 31, Folder 23-37)
  - Seneca County Annual Reports, 1998-2001 (Box 68)
  - Steuben County Annual Reports, 1944-1960 (Box 32, Folder 1-17)
  - Steuben County Annual Reports, 1996, 1998, 2000 (Box 68)
  - Suffolk County Annual Reports, 1944-1947, 1949-1957 (Box 32, Folder 18-30)
  - Suffolk County Annual Reports, 1958-1960 (Box 33, Folder 1-3)
  - Suffolk County Annual Reports, 1996-2000 (Box 68)
  - Sullivan County Annual Reports, 1951-1960 (Box 33, Folder 4-13)
  - Sullivan County Annual Reports, 1996-2000 (Box 68)
  - Syracuse Annual Reports, 1944-1959 (Box 38, Folder 7-22)
  - Tioga County Annual Reports, 1951-1960 (Box 33, Folder 14-30)
  - Tioga County Annual Reports, 1996-2001 (Box 68)
  - Tompkins County Annual Reports, 1944-1953 (Box 33, Folder 31-40)
  - Tompkins County Annual Reports, 1954-1960 (Box 34, Folder 1-7)
  - Tompkins County Annual Reports, 1997 (Box 68)
  - Ulster County Annual Reports, 1944-1960 (Box 34, Folder 8-24)
  - Ulster County Annual Reports, 1996-1997, 1999, 2001 (Box 68)
  - Warren County Annual Reports, 1944-1954 (Box 34, Folder 25-35)
  - Warren County Annual Reports, 1955-1960 (Box 35, Folder 1-6)
  - Warren County Annual Reports, 1996-1997, 1999-2000 (Box 68)
  - Washington County Annual Reports, 1944-1960 (Box 35, Folder 7-23)
  - Washington County Annual Reports, 1993-1999 (Box 68)
  - Wayne County Annual Reports, 1944-1958 (Box 35, Folder 24-38)
  - Wayne County Annual Reports, 1959-1960 (Box 36, Folder 1-2)
  - Wayne County Annual Reports, 1994, 1996-2000 (Box 68)
  - Westchester County Annual Reports, 1944-1960 (Box 36, Folder 3-19)
  - Westchester County Annual Reports, 1998 (Box 68)
  - Wyoming County Annual Reports, 1944-1960 (Box 36, Folder 20-36)
  - Wyoming County Annual Reports, 1996-1997, 1999-2001 (Box 68)
  - Yates County Annual Reports, 1948-1960 (Box 37, Folder 1-13)
  - Yates County Annual Reports, 1999-2000 (Box 68)
  - County Annual Reports - including CD #3238 and #3239, 2004-2005 (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - County Annual Reports, 2006-2007 (Box 89, Folder 9)
  - Cooperative Extension Initiatives, Plans and Reports
  - The Organization of a Rural Community-T.E. Carver (Box 83, Folder 39)
  - The Cooperative Extension Service in Agriculture and Home Economics -Dwight Sanderson, 1997 (Box 83, Folder 40)
  - Your Career as a County Home Demonstration Agent, 1945 (Box 83, Folder 41)
  - Preliminary Plans for a Rural Housing Program for New York State -Northeastern States Regional Housing Workshop, Ithaca, 1946 (Box 83, Folder 42)
  - A Look Ahead in Extension Work-Repot of Extension Directors, Jackson's Mill, West Virginia, 1947 (Box 83, Folder 43)
  - Working Conditions of Extension Workers (U.S.D.A. Reoprt), 1947 (Box 83, Folder 44)
  - Radio as a Source of Agricultural and Homemaking Information-U.S.D.A., 1948 (Box 83, Folder 45)
  - Some Major Trends in Cooperative Extension Work-U.S.D.A., 1948-1949 (Box 83, Folder 46)
  - Survey of Extension Work in the Urban Areas of the Northeast, 1949 (Box 83, Folder 47)
  - Report on Extension Service in Agriculture and Home Economics by M. E. Robinson-State University of New York, 1950 (Box 83, Folder 48)
  - The Organization of the New York State Extension Service- Andrew J. Nichols-U.S.D.A., 1951 (Box 83, Folder 49)
  - A Study of Problems and Practices of Cooperative and General Extension Services in Land-Grant Colleges and Universities (Senate Committee on Problems of Urban Educational Extension), 1954 (Box 83, Folder 50)
  - County Extension Headquarters Building and Equipment-Ruby Loper, 1956 (Box 83, Folder 51)
  - How to Make a Study of Extension Agents' Use of Time-Laurel Sabrosky-U.S.D.A., 1956 (Box 83, Folder 52)
  - Research Summaries, Division of Extension Research and Training, U.S.D.A., 1956-1957 (Box 83, Folder 53)
  - Commission on Increased Use of Agricultural Products, 1957 (Box 83, Folder 54)
  - History of Extension and the College of Agriculture, 1958 (Box 83, Folder 55)
  - Report of the Field Representative Program of the New York State College of Agriculture-Carl Gortzig, 1958 (Box 83, Folder 56)
  - Agricultural Research and Extension-Report by William Tyler, 1958 (Box 83, Folder 57)
  - Professional Ethics-Cooperative Extension Educators-M.C. Bond, 1959 (Box 83, Folder 58)
  - The Evolving Low Income Problems in Agriculture-Frank Welch, 1959 (Box 83, Folder 59)
  - Report on the Committee on Problems and Practices of Cooperative and General Extension, 1962 (Box 86, Folder 14)
  - Cooperative Extension Service Matters for Policy Consideration by Cornell University Officials, 1964 (Box 86, Folder 15)
  - Outline for Developing Cooperative Extension Programs, 1964 (Box 86, Folder 16)
  - Title I of the Higher Education Act of 1965 (Box 86, Folder 17)
  - Report-Task Force for Disadvantaged Audiences, 1966 (Box 86, Folder 18)
  - Educational Leadership - Extension Home Economist, 1967-1968 (Box 85, Folder 32)
  - Contemporary Responsibility of Extension Work in Home Economics, Undated (Box 86, Folder 19)
  - Community Gardens Bill, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - Accomplishment Reports - 4-H Youth Enrollment Report, 1985 (Box 85, Folder 33)
  - Delivering Community Agriculture Program in New York State and Targeted Audiences, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 20)
  - Cornell Cooperative Extension Statewide Major Programs, 1988-1991 (Box 49, Folder 21)
  - Report of the Committee-Future of CCE System, 1987 (Box 49, Folder 22)
  - Report of the Ad Hoc Committee on staff for CCE, 1987 (Box 49, Folder 24)
  - Cornell Cooperative Extension System Program Staffing Plan, 1988 (Box 49, Folder 31)
  - Cornell Cooperative Extension System-Staffing the System, 1988 (Box 49, Folder 32)
  - Program Staffing Plan, 1988-03 (Box 49, Folder 33)
  - Mission and Vision: Cooperative Extension Strategic Plan, 1996 (Box 49, Folder 38)
  - Your New York State Executive Service (1963), Report for Organization Plan for CCE in New York State by Director AA. Johnson 1964 (Box 49, Folder 41)
  - Extension Service USDA Interaction from 1914 to 1977 with National Issues and with State Extension Services, 1987 (Box 49, Folder 48)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity (OEO) and Cornell University-Agreements and Projects, 1960-1969 (Box 58, Folder 30)
  - 4-H Relationships with the National Jr. Vegetable Growers Assn., 1996 (Box 58, Folder 31)
  - Cornell Cooperation Extension Satellite Network (CCESN) and Distance Learning Task Group Report, 1996 (Box 58, Folder 32)
  - Cornell Cooperative Extension-in New York City-memos, reports, 1989-1995 (Box 58, Folder 34)
  - Cornell Cooperative Extension in New York City-memos, reports, 1992 (Box 58, Folder 35)
  - Cornell Cooperative Extension-in New York City-reports, 1988-1993 (Box 58, Folder 36)
  - Toward an Integrated Information System, 1985-10 (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - National Initiatives, 1986-1988 (Box 74, Folder 13)
  - National Initiatives, 1988-1992 (Box 74, Folder 14)
  - 75th Anniversary of the Cornell Cooperative Extension System, 1986 (Box 74, Folder 15)
  - National Extension Initiative Network, 1991-1993 (Box 74, Folder 16)
  - ADEC Digital Satellite Network Proposal, 1989-1999 (Box 74, Folder 17-18)
  - Program Management and Accountability System, 1992-1995 (Box 74, Folder 19)
  - Strategic Planning Reducing Risks/Increasing Capacity-Casowasco Conference, 1994-05 (Box 66, Folder 35)
  - Satellite Network (CCESN) and Distance Learning Task Group Report, 1996 (Box 66, Folder 36)
  - Agriculture Weather Project and Extension Service, 1997 (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - (CCTTS) Partnerships in Action Tour, 1997-05 (Box 74, Folder 20)
  - Government Performance Results Act (GPRA) Annual Report, 1998 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Government Performance Results Act (GPRA) Annual Report, 1999 (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - Government Performance Results Act (GPRA) Annual Report, 1998 (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Agriculture Systems Initiative, 1998-2000 (Box 74, Folder 21)
  - Agriculture Systems Initiative, 1999 (Box 74, Folder 22)
  - Classification/Compensation Study, 1999-2000 (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - Cornell Cooperative Extension Boards-Report 2004-2005; Newsletter (1999), 1999-2005 (Box 66, Folder 37)
  - Agriculture Systems Initiative, 2000-2001 (Box 74, Folder 23)
  - Cornell Cooperative Extension Week and National 4-H Week, 2000 (Box 74, Folder 24)
  - Williams Communications Contract-Internet Connection, 2000 (Box 74, Folder 25)
  - Revitalization Plan, 2000-2001 (Box 74, Folder 26)
  - Learning Center Proposals, 2001 (Box 74, Folder 27)
  - Signature System, 2001 (Box 74, Folder 28)
  - Sun Grant Initiative, 2001-2005 (Box 74, Folder 29)
  - South Central (CCTTS) Area Dairy and Field Crops Program, 2002 (Box 74, Folder 30)
  - Terrorism - Combating It, 2002 (Box 74, Folder 31)
  - Environmental Sustainability Research Initiative, 2003-04 (Box 74, Folder 32)
  - Associations-Campus Connections Study, 2001 (Box 77, Folder 18)
  - Human Ecology Departments Annual Reports, 2001-06 (Box 77, Folder 19)
  - Our Food - Our Future - Enhancing Community Food Security Through Local Action - Program Guide, 2002-06 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Our Food - Our Future, 2002-06; V-7156 (Box 1)
  - Northeast Regional Food Guides, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Annual Deans Report Summaries of Priorities, 2002 (Box 77, Folder 20)
  - Northern New York Agricultural Development Program Report-Clinton, Essex, Franklin Counties, 2002-2003 (Box 77, Folder 21)
  - State of Cornell Cooperative Extension:An Assessment, 2002-2003 (Box 77, Folder 22)
  - "The Future of American Agriculture and the Land Grant University: Towards a Sustainable, Healthful, and Entrepreneurial Food System", 2003 (Box 77, Folder 23)
  - Annual Reports-Various Programs, 2003-2005 (Box 77, Folder 24)
  - Annual Reports-Various Programs, 2003-2005 (Box 77, Folder 25)
  - Cornell Cooperative Extension Annual Report, 2007 (Box 78, Folder 15)
  - Audit Reports, 2004-2005 (Box 77, Folder 26)
  - New York City Program Review Report, 2005-05 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Cornell University's Responsibility in New York State to Provide Leadership and Supervision for Cornell Cooperative Extension Programming, 2005-12 (Box 89, Folder 30)